Did I not warn you before
If you hurt her again
I'll make you disappear
Seventh Prince
I did it all for you
Once Li Zhi'an reveals the location of the Dragon Jade treasure
Your ascension to the throne will be within reach
Who gave you permission to speculate about my intentions
You only need to follow orders
If the Seventh Prince truly blames me
Then just kill me
After all, I've already shed heart's blood for you
One more wound won't matter
Whatever you give me
I'll gladly accept
Keep a close eye on Zhu Huaichen
That's your real mission
Zhu Huaijin, why are you rebelling against Zhu Huaichen
For you
For me
I vow to protect you for all eternity
No more getting hurt
This is what I owe you
Lee Ji-an, snap out of it
You can't fall into this
That Zhu guy is as bad as his gang
None of them can be trusted
Maybe she's after the dragon jade on my back
Stop dwelling on it
Her behavior was so unusual
Could she really see it?
Did she know about the gu worm in the cup?
Impossible, I tested her
She didn't even avoid the boiling oil
There's no way she could see
Then you really should stop thinking about it
That kiss was meant for Zhu Huaichen
Not for you
Zhu Huaichen doesn't deserve it
Neither do I
Lee Ji-an
If you win, I'll make you pay the price
We need to turn Li Zhi'an into a blind man that no one wants
This will require your hard work
But rest assured
After we put the mask on you
You won't disgrace our Nanliang royal family
Let's go
My seventh brother is truly loyal to me
He personally lured the snake
This snake-luring is crucial for His Highness to punish Li Zhi'an
And obtain the Dragon Jade treasure
I will personally oversee this matter
Zhu Huaichen
This time I must protect Zhi'an
I absolutely won't let you succeed
This might be our last meeting in this lifetime
Zhi'an
You must live well from now on
Sir, why are you covered in wounds?
In these mountain wilds
Did you encounter wild beasts?
Do you need help?
No need, I'm waiting for someone
Miss
The weather is about to change
You should head down the mountain quickly
Why?
Why couldn't I change anything?
Why is it still like this?
Why are you so kind-hearted
To turn back
You wouldn't understand
This is what I owe her